relenta.com 2017-12-15

# Privacy Policy | Relenta

Relenta, Inc. (“Relenta”) operates several websites and services including relenta.com and relenta.net. It is Relenta’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites and services.

##### Customer data ownership

All user information stored or transferred to Relenta customer accounts is governed by our [Terms of Service](http://www.relenta.com/tos). Although Relenta owns the data storage, databases and the Relenta site, customers retain all rights to their data. Relenta will not use the data in our databases for any purpose other than providing the services to our customers.

##### Website visitors

Like most website operators, Relenta collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Relenta’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Relenta’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Relenta may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, such as trends in the usage of its website.

Relenta also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on our blogs or forums. Relenta only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally identifying information as described below, except that blog or forum commenter IP addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog or forum where the comment was left.

##### Gathering of personally identifying information

Certain visitors to Relenta’s websites choose to interact with Relenta in ways that require Relenta to gather personally identifying information. The amount and type of information that Relenta gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for one of Relenta services to provide their name, company name, and contact information including email address. We collect email addresses of those who communicate with us via email or by submitting a contact form on our websites. Those who engage in transactions with Relenta – by purchasing certain services, for example – are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, Relenta collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Relenta. Relenta does not disclose personally identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website- or service-related activities.

##### Protection of certain personally-identifying information

Relenta discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Relenta’s behalf or to provide services available at Relenta’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Relenta’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Relenta will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Relenta discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Relenta believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Relenta, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an Relenta website and have supplied your email address, Relenta may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Relenta and our products. We primarily use our various product blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Relenta takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

##### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Relenta uses cookies to help Relenta identify and track visitors, their usage of Relenta website, and their website access preferences. Relenta visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Relenta’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Relenta’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

##### Business transfers

If Relenta, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Relenta goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Relenta may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

##### Privacy policy changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Relenta may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Relenta’s sole discretion. Relenta encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
